bhinsights.com 2016-10-24

# Privacy and Security | B&H Photo Video

**Security:**  
Please note: The following only applies to B&H's main website ([www.bhphotovideo.com](https://www.bhphotovideo.com/)) but not to our blog "B&H Explora" ([www.bhphotovideo.com/explora](https://www.bhphotovideo.com/explora/)). The security of your personal information is very important to us. In an effort to protect your personal information, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology with 256 bit encryption. If your browser supports SSL (most current browsers do), it will automatically encrypt the information you provide to us on the secure pages on our site, before sending it over the internet. B&H has obtained a digital certificate from Cybertrust, a leading provider of internet trust services. B&H's website is also tested and certified daily by ScanAlert to receive its Hacker Safe Certification which ensures that the website passes the FBI/SANS Internet Security Test.

When visiting a page on our site that includes any of your personal information, the bottom of your browser window will display an icon of a closed lock or an unbroken key (depending upon your browser). This indicates that you have successfully connected with our secure server.

To authenticate the security of your connection before submitting any of your personal information, you can double-click on the icon to display our digital certificate.

Some browser versions and some firewalls do not permit communication through secure servers. In that case, we suggest that you visit the B&H super store, or contact us by phone, or fax your order to us.

**Cookies:**  
When you visit our site, we will ask your browser to place a permanent "cookie" (a very small text file) on your computer. If your browser is configured to accept cookies, it will accept the cookie and place it on your computer's hard drive. We collect this information to analyze where our customers are coming from and how often they visit our site. We also collect certain technical information from your computer, like your IP address and the address of a referring web site, if any. This information will allow us to enhance our site to match our customer's preferences. This information is used only for the benefit of B&H and you, our customer.  
You can visit our site without cookies if you choose to do so. However, please be aware that some features of the site may not function properly or may be slower if you refuse cookies. To visit our site without cookies, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies or to notify you when a cookie is set. Check the browser's help menu to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

**Registration:**  
In order to identify who you are, we suggest that you register and log in when you visit our site. This allows us to provide you with your "Order Status" and other information that is uniquely yours.

**Right to Access/Correct Your Information:**  
You have the right to access all the personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain, and can do so by phoning 800-606-6969 or 212-444-6615, mailing (420 Ninth Avenue, New York, NY 10001, USA), or contacting us by [e-mail](https://www.bhphotovideo.com/bnh/controller/home?O=helpcenter&A=getpage&Q=contactForm.jsp&destination=status%40bhphotovideo.com). We use this procedure to safeguard your information. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows the error.  
If you place an order with a ship-to address that differs from your bill-to address, we retain this information as well. You can modify or correct this information by following the procedure described above. Such information is used at your request to ship purchased merchandise and may also be used for marketing purposes, but will not be sold to any third parties.

**What Information Is Collected:**  
When you choose to place an order with us, you are invited to log in (optional), so that we can identify who you are. As a newcomer, it will be suggested that you register for future identification. The registration page asks you to enter your name, a user ID, a password and your email address. You can update this information at any time by clicking on the "my account" link at the top of every page and selecting "update account information."

**Placing an Order:**  
When you decide to place an order, you are asked to complete an order form. The order form requires your name, billing and shipping addresses, credit card number, expiration date and CID#. You should also include other information fields such as your telephone number, to allow us to contact you regarding your order if necessary. This information is collected to make your shopping experience with us as smooth and pleasant as possible. It is used only for the benefit of B&H and you, our customer.

**Links:**  
Our site contains links to manufacturers and other related sites for your benefit. B&H is not responsible for the privacy practices, security, or content of such websites. If you click on one of these links, you will be redirected to their website and, in doing so, you may provide information directly to them. Therefore, you should refer to their privacy policies to understand how they handle your information and what choices are available to you.

**Relationships/Sharing Information:**  
B&H maintains special relationships with a number of secure business partners. For your security or benefit, when you make a purchase, we may share information about you and the transaction with other companies for many reasons including verification, fraud prevention, credit card authorization, US Government policy compliance and shipping purposes. We also may be required to disclose an individual's personal information in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

B&H may share account or other information when we are required by law (e.g., in response to subpoenas, court orders, etc.) or to protect our interests or property. This may include sharing information, at B&H's discretion, with other companies, lawyers, credit bureaus, agents or government agencies in connection with issues related to export compliance, fraud, credit or debt collection.

You agree that B&H may use personal information provided by you in order to conduct appropriate anti-fraud and export compliance checks. Personal information that you provide may be disclosed to a credit reference, fraud prevention agency or US Government agency, which may keep a record of that information.

B&H also shares information with outside companies that perform services for B&H. For example, when a customer signs up for our email newsletters, B&H will provide the customer's email address to third party email distribution companies that transmit emails on behalf of B&H. Your email address will not be used by these companies for any purpose other than for the transmission of emails for B&H.

We may retain outside companies to assist us in managing our customer information database or to update and correct customer information for future marketing purposes. B&H takes steps to ensure the confidentiality of your information and to make sure it is not used for other purposes.

B&H has carefully selected a few companies to assist us in better understanding how our customers use our site. We will place cookies on your computer to collect information. The information that is collected through these cookies tells us things, such as which search engine referred you, how you navigated around our site, which pages you browsed, what you purchased and what traffic is driven by banner ads and emails. The companies analyze the information they collect from our site and return it to us through a secure connection. We use this information to help us understand your interests in our site and how to better serve you. It also helps us provide you with more personalized product offerings.

In case of onward transfer to third parties of data of EU individuals received pursuant to the EU-US Privacy Shield, as fully detailed below, B&H is potentially liable.

For more information about the companies with whom B&H shares customer information, please [contact us](https://www.bhphotovideo.com/find/contactForm.jsp).

**US-EU PRIVACY SHIELD**  
B&H complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Member Countries. B&H has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit:  

European citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact B&H at:   
Legal Department  
B & H Foto & Electronics Corp.   
440 Ninth Avenue  
New York, New York 10001  
Phone: 212-239-7500  
Web: [www.bhphotovideo.com](https://www.bhphotovideo.com/)  
Email: [legal@bhphotovideo.com](mailto:legal@bhphotovideo.com)

In compliance with the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles, B&H commits to resolve complaints under the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit [www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints](http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints) for more information and to file a complaint. 

**US-SWISS SAFE HARBOR**  
B&H complies with the US-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from Switzerland. B&H has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity, Access, and Enforcement. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles, the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles shall govern. To learn more about the US-Swiss Safe Harbor program, and to view our certification page, please visit: [www.export.gov/safeharbor/](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/)   
In compliance with the US-Swiss Safe Harbor principles, B&H commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact B&H at:   
Legal Department  
B & H Foto & Electronics Corp.   
440 Ninth Avenue  
New York, New York 10001  
Phone: 212-239-7500  
Web: [www.bhphotovideo.com](https://www.bhphotovideo.com/)  
Email: [legal@bhphotovideo.com](mailto:legal@bhphotovideo.com)

B&H has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-Swiss Safe Harbor to an independent dispute resolution mechanism operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit [www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints](http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints) for more information and to file a complaint.  
B&H is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission ('FTC'). Please note that if your complaint is not resolved through the above-mentioned channels, under limited circumstances, a binding arbitration option may be available before a Privacy Shield Panel. 

**Use of Information:**  
We may use your information in a number of ways, including the following:

  * In order to serve you better, we may combine the information you provide us online, in our superstore and through our catalogues. We use that information to improve your overall shopping experience.
  * To improve the content on our website. For example, we may use cookies to find out which parts of our site or our products are visited most often.
  * To enhance your online shopping experience.
  * For marketing and promotional purposes.

**Mail & SPAM Issues:**  
You may request the B&H catalogue and brochures by mail or email to periodically receive notification of specials that may be of interest to you. B&H will never SPAM or send unsolicited materials based on information collected at our site. Registrants may opt out of receiving materials from us at any time by contacting us with such request. Please contact us via [email](https://www.bhphotovideo.com/bnh/controller/home?O=helpcenter&A=getpage&Q=contactForm.jsp&destination=status%40bhphotovideo.com), by telephone 800-606-6969 or 212-444-6615, by fax 212-239-7549, or via mail (420 Ninth Avenue, New York, NY 10001. Enclose a copy of the mailing label). Include your name, address and other information as it appears on the mailing label and indicate "Do not mail".

**Our Commitment to Children's Privacy:**  
We never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, nor is any part of our website structured to attract anyone under 13.

**If Security or Privacy Is Still of Concern to You:**  
If you do not want to receive promotional email from B&H, please [ click here](https://www.bhphotovideo.com/bnh/controller/home?O=privacy&A=changeSubscribtion&Q=)  
Note: Once you have submitted your request you should assume that it has been successfully received and your request is being processed. Please allow us a reasonable period from when the request was received to complete the removal.

Our transaction security, combined with our privacy guarantee, should satisfy your concerns regarding online ordering. Keep in mind, however, that you have a number of alternate choices available for doing business with B&H:

1\. You can order online without sending your credit card number over the internet. Just complete our online order form, print and fax it to us.

2\. If you prefer, you can always call 800-606-6969 or 212-444-6615 to place your order by telephone.

3\. We encourage you to visit the B&H midtown Manhattan SuperStore and deal directly with one of B&H's professionally trained sales associates.

If you have any questions regarding this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can [contact our Web Support Team.](https://www.bhphotovideo.com/bnh/controller/home?O=PrivacySecurity.jsp&A=getpage&Q=contactForm.jsp&destination=websupport)

**Changes to B &H Privacy Policy:**  
By visiting our site you consent to our collection and use of your information as described in this policy. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy and related business practices at any time by posting updated text on this site.

**California Privacy Rights**  
If you are a California resident, you have the right to receive: (a) information identifying all third-party companies to whom B&H may have disclosed, within the past year, personal information pertaining to you and your family for that company's direct marketing purposes; and (b) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. To obtain this information, please email your request. Please allow 30 days for a response.
